contenko.com 2014-12-23

# Privacy Policy

### 1\. INTRODUCTION

Welcome to Contenko! This Privacy Policy applies to all users of Contenko.com (the “Site”), and describes the collection and use of personal information (such as full name or address), and non-personally identifiable information (such as computer information, demographics or Site usage). The Site is hosted and operated in the United States. 

If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please notify us immediately using the contact link on the Site. 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our online privacy practices regarding information you submit, information we collect, and how we may use and share user information. 

###  2\. INFORMATION SUBMITTED BY USERS 

You may provide us with certain personal information while using the Site. For example, if you choose to contact us by email, we will collect your name, email address and any other information you may provide us, and keep a record of this communication. 

Providing personal information is voluntary and you have the choice not to disclose any information. We will use such information to communicate with you, provide you with services on the Site, and for ongoing recordkeeping purposes, as required by law. 

###  3\. INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED 

**Accessing the Site.** When users access the Site, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected, such as IP address, computer or mobile device type, browser type, operating system, Site usage data, and referring and redirected website addresses. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Site, our servers receive and record information about your computer or mobile device, operating system and browser, IP address, and other software or hardware information. We may assign and utilize a unique identifier to your computer or mobile device. This collected data may also be supplemented and correlated with other information obtained from third parties or submitted by users. 

**Tracking and Data Collection Technologies.** We may use cookies and other tracking technologies, such as browser cookies, pixels, web beacons, log files, and Adobe Flash technology, which may also include anonymous unique identifiers. Websites transmit this data when users request a web page and store the data on your computer in order to access information when you make subsequent requests for web pages. These technologies may be used to collect and store information about your usage of the Site and other sites or content affiliated or partnered with us, such as pages you have visited, search queries you have run, links you have clicked and advertisements you have seen. We may also use these tracking technologies to supplement and correlate such use with other information and data obtained from you or third parties, including third parties who use similar tracking and data collection technologies described above. 

**Third Party Tracking and Data Collection.** Third parties that support the Site by serving advertisements or content, or providing other services, such as tracking site usage or providing content and ads, may also use cookies, pixels, web beacons and other tracking and data collection technologies described above to collect information about Site users. We do not control these third parties and their use of these tracking technologies is governed by the privacy policies of the third parties using such technologies. 

For more information about third party ad networks using these technologies, please visit [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). 

**Do Not Track Settings.** Please note that the Site does not accommodate or respond to unique browser or privacy settings, such as "Do Not Track". 

### 4\. INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE

We may share your personal information with non-affiliated third parties when we believe disclosure is permitted by you or authorized by this Privacy Policy. We may also share any user information with any corporate parent, subsidiary or affiliate. 

We may use and share your user information as follows: 

**To manage and maintain the Site.** We use the information we collect from and about users to maintain and operate the Site, to measure and improve the Site, to personalize your experience by delivering relevant content and advertisements, and to provide customer support. We may use aggregated, anonymous data about use of the Site to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy. 

**To allow third parties to assist us in managing the Site.** We may make your non-public personal information available to third party providers, such as advertising partners, vendors, agents or other contractors, who help manage the Site or provide advertising, content or other services. Such examples include: serving third party advertising, managing or supporting services or features, storing and processing data, and Site administration. 

**To contact you.** We may send administrative or promotional materials and notifications related to the Site to the email address you may have provided to us. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from us, follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each promotional email. 

**To protect our rights or comply with the law.** There may be instances when we may disclose user information without providing notice or choice, including situations where we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (a) protect or defend our legal rights or property; (b) protect the safety and security of Site users or members of the public; (c) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (d) comply with the law or legal process. 

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If we sell the underlying Site business or assets, or are involved in a merger or other similar transaction to transfer business ownership of the Site, we may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in such transaction. 

### 5\. SECURITY

Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the Internet can ever be guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under our control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal information you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk. If you believe that your interaction with the Site is no longer secure, please notify us of the problem at the contact information provided on the Site. 

### 6\. DISCLAIMER

YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE SITE IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS-IS" AND "WITH ALL FAULTS" BASIS, AND WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OR CONDITION, EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY. YOU AGREE THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OR LOSSES THAT ARISE FROM YOUR USE OF THE SITE. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY ASPECT OF THE SITE, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USE OF THE SITE.
